Contact

lindsay11289@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lindsay-monroe-491a4689 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Healthcare
Cpr Certified

Lindsay Monroe

Travel Nurse (RN, BSN) at HealthTrust Workforce Solutions New Orleans, Louisiana

Summary

Experienced Travel Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the staffing and recruiting industry. Skilled in Patient Advocacy, Medication Administration, Patient Education, Vital Signs, and Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR). Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science in Nursing (RN, BSN) focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Louisiana State University Health Sciences Center.

Experience

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions Travel Nurse (RN, BSN) May 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months) San Antonio, Texas

Aya Healthcare Travel Nurse (RN, BSN) June 2016 - May 2018 (2 years)

West Jefferson Medical Center Registered Nurse May 2015 - June 2016 (1 year 2 months)

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington Family Nurse Practitioner, MSN · (2019 - 2022)

Louisiana State University Health Sciences Center
Bachelor of Science in Nursing (RN, BSN), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2011 - 2014)